<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Atalanta Systems Ltd]]></title>
  <link href="http://atalanta-systems.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://atalanta-systems.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-18T22:41:10+03:00</updated>
  <id>http://atalanta-systems.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Stephen Nelson-Smith]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atalanta selected for Strategic Blue’s Preferred Partner Programme]]></title>
    <link href="http://atalanta-systems.com/blog/2012/10/18/atalanta-selected-for-strategic-blues-preferred-partner-programme/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-18T21:52:00+03:00</updated>
    <id>http://atalanta-systems.com/blog/2012/10/18/atalanta-selected-for-strategic-blues-preferred-partner-programme</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Atalanta Systems is excited to announce that it has been selected as the first professional services consultancy to join Cloud Broker-Dealer Strategic Blue’s preferred partner programme.  Strategic Blue specialise in financial intermediation of the cloud, and are able to ensure Cloud buyers can purchase on terms which suit their own requirements, rather than those of the Cloud providers.  With established relationships with multiple Cloud vendors, Strategic Blue is also able to provide a single bill for multiple providers, and find the best cloud deals in an increasingly competitive market.</p>

<p>Companies looking at moving to the cloud, or simply moving to a different cloud provider who more accurately meets their technical or financial requirements typically need help in making this idea a reality.  As experts in Cloud Automation, Atalanta Systems is able to migrate IT infrastructures from traditional in-house hosting to the cloud, or from one cloud provider to another.  Grounded in their expertise in Opscode’s leading automation framework, Chef, customers running Windows, Linux or even traditional Unix systems can have their infrastructures modelled as code, and then redeployed in one or more clouds appropriate to their requirements.</p>

<p>Eager to make their financial services offering more accessible, Strategic Blue can now provide migration services and technical consultancy under the same single bill, via its partnership with Atalanta.</p>

<p><strong>Atalanta Systems CEO, Helena Nelson-Smith</strong>, explains the significance:</p>

<p><em>“We’re delighted with our partnership with Strategic Blue.  As a small cloud consultancy, we’ve focussed most of our business development on referral and recommendation, but this partnership with Strategic Blue opens up a whole new source of customers, all with the kinds of problems we have a proven track record in solving.  It’s a tremendously exciting development!”</em></p>

<p>Atalanta co-founder and principal consultant Stephen Nelson-Smith will join the Strategic Blue management team as CTO, with a mandate to grow Strategic Blue’s own cloud professional services capabilities through the implementation of the new partnership programme, and to serve as technical evangelist supporting Strategic Blue’s vision to embrace the economic future of Cloud, understanding and resolving the technical hurdles to unlocking a market in which Cloud becomes an efficiently traded commodity.</p>

<p><strong>Stephen</strong> says:</p>

<p><em>“I’ve worked hard to build a team of cloud automation specialists at Atalanta, and the opportunity to apply that expertise to the many organizations seeking to make the move to the cloud, or to derisk or maximise their financial investment in the cloud fits perfectly with Atalanta’s mantra that as DevOps professionals, our aim is always to be delivering value to the business.  Strategic Blue’s vision makes perfect sense to me, and being a part of its realisation is incredibly exciting.”</em></p>

<p><strong>James Mitchell, Strategic Blue CEO</strong>, adds:</p>

<p><em>“I’ve worked with Stephen as an Atalanta client and as a referrer of business to Atalanta, and his combination of technical depth, client-facing expertise, and ability to grasp and care about client’s business objectives is impressive.  We’re thrilled to be bringing him in as Strategic Blue’s CTO, and we’re sure he’ll be a great asset to us and our clients.  We are also very excited to have now formalised our partnership with Atalanta, as we have come to recognise that their skill-set is highly prized by our clients.”</em></p>

<p>Stephen remains board advisor to Atalanta Systems, and will continue to provide high touch and C-level consulting, and Opscode Chef training and implementation services under the Atalanta brand, alongside his new role at Strategic Blue.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
